Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2013
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Composer Francis Heery at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3544 composer.tif (Image-file jib2013_186)
- Student composers Jenny Beck, Eric Stewart, and Valentina Velkovska at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Composers Valentina Velkovska Jenny Beck.tif (Image-file jib2013_187)
- Audience for Megan Beugger's piece in Chamber Music performance at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3554audience for 4 pm performance by composer Megan Beug.tif (Image-file jib2013_188)
- Percussionist Tom Kolor and flutist Barry Crawford perform Crack by Clinton Haycraft at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Tom Kolor Barry Crawford composer Clint Haycraft.tif (Image-file jib2013_189)
- Percussionist Tom Kolor and flutist Barry Crawford congratulate composer Clinton Haycraft after a performance of Crack at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3558Composer Clint Hayraft Tom Kolor Barry Crawford.tif (Image-file jib2013_190)
- Percussionist Tom Kolor and flutist Barry Crawford onstage with composer Clinton Haycraft after a performance of Crack at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Composer Clint Haycraft Tom Kolor Barry Crawford.tif (Image-file jib2013_191)
- Matthew Geiger performing Milton Babbitt's Concerto piccolino at June in Buffalo Performance Institute 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3565Matthew Geiger playing Milton Babbitt.tif (Image-file jib2013_192)
- June in Buffalo Performance Institute participants and faculty for 2013: Kevin McFarland, Manuel Laufer, Jonathan Golove, Nicholas Emmanuel, Ari Streisfeld, Eric Huebner, Hangyu Bai, Ross Aftel, Michiko Saiki, John Pickford Richards, Jade Conlee, Matthew Geiger, and T. J. Borden, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3578Performing Institute and Eric Huebner.tif (Image-file jib2013_193)
- Display of programs and scores at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-08, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3594scores.tif (Image-file jib2013_194)
- Pianist Geoffrey Burleson at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3668Geoff Burleson Pianist--.tif (Image-file jib2013_195)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas at rehearsal with Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2013, with conductor JoAnn Falletta kneeling to the right, 2013-06-09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3685Augusta Reed Thomas with Buffalo Philharmonic Orches.tif (Image-file jib2013_196)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas at rehearsal with Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: _MG_3687Augusta Reed Thomas with the Buffalo Philharmonic Or.tif (Image-file jib2013_197)
- JoAnn Falletta conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic orchestra in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-09, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra.tif (Image-file jib2013_198)
- Composer Brian Ferneyhough onstage with violinist Irvine Arditti and members of Signal Ensemble and their conductor Brad Lubman after the performance of Ferneyhough's Terrain at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer Brian Ferneyhough Irving Arditti with SIGNAL Brad L.tif (Image-file jib2013_199)
- Conductor Brad Lubman asking members of the SIGNAL ensemble to stand after a performance at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-10, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: SIGNAL Brad Lubman conductor.tif (Image-file jib2013_200)
- Audience at Brian Ferneyhough lecture at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-13, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ferneyhough lecture.tif (Image-file jib2013_201)
- Composer Raphael Cendo acknowledging conductor Jean-Philippe Wurtz and members of Ensemble Linea after a performance at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-13, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble Linea composer Raphael Cendo.tif (Image-file jib2013_202)
- JACK Quartet lecture at June in Buffalo 2013, 2013-06-13, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Jack Quartet lecture.tif (Image-file jib2013_203)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo (Festival) (Buffalo, N.Y.)--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Digital photographs; Portrait photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals is available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.